A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82) FA209
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (A82), 1944-2002; 8; 164.55 Cubic Feet Boxes 1077-1506. 392 letter-sized boxes, 24 legal-sized boxes, 6 half-letter-sized boxes, 6 half-legal-sized boxes, one 21x17 short oversized box, one 18x14 short oversized box, and 3 containers; Document boxes 1077-1506.
  - Thailand, 617; 4.5 Cubic Feet 10 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box and 1 half-legal box
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Kanto, Uthai, 1974-1980 (Box 1493, Folder 10112A)
      - Impithuksa, Viroch, 1974-1979 (Box 1493, Folder 10113)
      - Impithuksa, Viroch, 1974-1979 (Box 1493, Folder 10113A)
      - Boonyatharokul, Wiboon, 1974-1979 (Box 1493, Folder 10114)
      - Boonyatharokul, Wiboon, 1974-1979 (Box 1493, Folder 10114A)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, S
      - Bangkok - University Development, 1963-1974, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 1494, Folder 10115-10117)
      - University of Thammasat - Agricultural Supply in Thailand, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 1494, Folder 10118)
        Folder 10118 contains Evaluation
      - University of Thammasat - Asian University Planning, 1979-1980 (Box 1494, Folder 10119)
        Folder 10119 contains Evaluation
      - University of Thammasat - Economics - Travel, 1978-1979, 1982 (Box 1494, Folder 10120-10121)
        Folder 10121 (Evaluation)
      - University of Thammasat - Rector Prapasna Auychai, 1978-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 1494, Folder 10122-10123)
        Folder 10123 (Evaluation)
      - University of Thammasat - Rice Economics, 1974, 1977-1978, 1981-1983 (Box 1494, Folder 10124-10125)
        Folder 10124 (I) contains Evaluation, Folder 10125 (II)
  - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 626; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM) - Hawaii, 214
      - Oceanic Foundation, 1971-1978 (Box 1495, Folder 10126-10132)
        Folder 10126 (I), Folders 10127-10131 (II), Folder 10132 (Evaluation)
      - Oceanic Foundation - Fishes Health Care, 1977-1980 (Box 1496, Folder 10133-10134)
        Folder 10134 (Evaluation)
      - Oceanic Foundation - Salmon Seeding, 1975-1979 (Box 1496, Folder 10135-10137)
        Folder 10137 (Evaluation)
      - University of Hawaii, 1973-1979, 1984 (Box 1496, Folder 10138-10140)
        Folder 10140 (Evaluation)
      - University of Hawaii - Salmon Seeding, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 1496, Folder 10141-10142)
        Folder 10142 (Evaluation)
  - Netherlands, 650; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
    - Netherlands - Social Sciences, S
      - Hague Academy of International Law, 1971-1976, 1978, 1982 (Box 1497, Folder 10143-10145)
  - Indonesia, 652; 1.61 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box and 3 letter document boxes
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Boediono, 1974-1979 (Box 1497, Folder 10146)
      - Boediono, 1974-1979 (Box 1497, Folder 10146A)
      - Djauhar Ismail, 1977-1979 (Box 1497, Folder 10147)
      - Djauhar Ismail, 1977-1979 (Box 1497, Folder 10147A)
      - Gaffar, Afan, 1975-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 1498, Folder 10148)
        Name also listed as Afan Gaffar Achmad and Afan Gaffar Ahmad; name changed to Afan Gaffar at his request, August 1976.
      - Gaffar, Afan, 1975-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 1498, Folder 10148A)
      - Jesmandt Situmorang, 1972-1981 (Box 1498, Folder 10149)
      - Jesmandt Situmorang, 1972-1981 (Box 1498, Folder 10149A)
      - Kuntowijoyo, 1970-1971, 1973-1980 (Box 1498, Folder 10150-10151)
      - Kuntowijoyo, 1970-1971, 1973-1980 (Box 1498, Folder 10150A)
      - Loekman, Soetrisno, 1973-1981 (Box 1498, Folder 10152-10153)
      - Loekman, Soetrisno, 1973-1981 (Box 1498, Folder 10152A)
      - Sanusi, Rossi, 1973-1979 (Box 1499, Folder 10154)
      - Sanusi, Rossi, 1973-1979 (Box 1499, Folder 10154A)
      - Sunardi, 1976-1980 (Box 1499, Folder 10155)
      - Sunardi, 1976-1980 (Box 1499, Folder 10155A)
      - Tohari, 1977-1979 (Box 1499, Folder 10156)
      - Tohari, 1977-1979 (Box 1499, Folder 10156A)
    - Indonesia - University Development, UD
      - Administration - Automobiles, 1972-1977 (Box 1499, Folder 10157)
      - Consultants (A-Z), 1971 (Box 1499, Folder 10158)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Land Cruiser, 1979-1980 (Box 1499, Folder 10159)
        Folder 10159 contains Evaluation
      - Gadjah Mada University - Master Plan, 1974 (Box 1499, Folder 10160)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Soybeans, 1975-1982 (Box 1499, Folder 10161-10163)
        Folder 10163 (Evaluation)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Soybeans: Supplementary Material (Box 1500, Folder 10164)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Tractor, 1975, 1977 (Box 1500, Folder 10165)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Upland Rice, 1972-1975, 1977 (Box 1500, Folder 10166)
        Folder 10166 contains Evaluation)
      - Medical Sciences - Consultants (A-Z), 1978-1980 (Box 1500, Folder 10167)
  - Belgium, 707; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Belgium - Social Sciences, S
      - Vrije Universiteit Brussel - African Child Spacing, 1977-1981 (Box 1500, Folder 10168-10171)
        Folder 10171 (Evaluation)
  - Romania, 783; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Romania - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Margineanu, Nicolae, 1979-1980 (Box 1500, Folder 10172)
  - Turkey, 805; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Ekse, Ali Osman, 1978-1981 (Box 1501, Folder 10173)
      - Ekse, Ali Osman, 1978-1981 (Box 1501, Folder 10173A)
  - Egypt, 812; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Egypt - Medical Sciences, A
      - Assiut University - Contraceptive Technology, 1977-1979, 1981-1983 (Box 1501, Folder 10174)
        Folder 10174 contains Evaluation
  - Israel, 825; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Hebrew University - Wastewater Management, 1974-1980 (Box 1501, Folder 10175-10177)
      Folder 10177 (Evaluation)
    - Hebrew University - Wastewater Management: Supplementary Material (Box 1501, Folder 10178-10179)
  - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries, 850; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Massachusetts, 224
      - Boston University - Public Enterprise Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 1502, Folder 10180)
      - Boston University - Public Enterprise Conference: Supplementary Material (Box 1502, Folder 10181-10184)
  - Photographs and Special Formats Separated from Project Files 1.8 (A82) (Box 1503)